David Conner Borkowski

Boulder, Colorado

Summary

Community advocate and self-motivated student passionate about extending experience to build the capacity of groups and individuals. Especially dedicated to raising voices of historically marginalized groups, promoting justice, equity, diversity, and inclusion (JEDI) initiatives, and utilizes teamwork and active listening to build equity in outdoor recreation.

Relevant Specialized Skills and Courses

- Stakeholder and Community Engagement
- Intermediate ArcGIS Online
- · Advanced Written and Verbal Communication Skills
- · Facilitation and Education
- Project Management and Collaboration
- · Data Management and Analysis
- · Photography, Videography, and Design

Education

University of Colorado Boulder - Masters for the Environment - Expected May 2024

GPA: 4.0

Specializing in Sustainability in the Outdoor Industry

Masters for the Environment Merit Scholarship

North Carolina State University – B.S. Electrical Engineering, B.S. Computer Engineering – May 2022

GPA: 4.0

Minors: Outdoor Leadership, Art and Design

Relevant Professional Experience

Masters in the Environment - Media Graduate Student Assistant - September 2022 to Present Kev Accomplishments:

Updated media database to not include external stock images.

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for building the media base that accurately represents the community.
- Manage videography and recording of guest speaker events.
- Assist in engaging prospective students at open houses and other visits.

Outdoor Adventures at NC State University – Instructor & Trip Lead – February 2019 to May 2022 Key Accomplishments:

- Achieved Trip Leader of the Year in 2022
- Managed relationships and set expectations to open a state-of-the-art climbing center.
- Collaborated with affinity groups to hold climbing related events.

Responsibilities:

- Carried out complex trip plans.
- Worked in cross-functional teams to support educational missions.
- Programmed year-long plans for all trip leads.

Volunteer Experience

Embedded Machine Learning Club at NC State University - Founder & COO - July 2021 to May 2022 Key Accomplishments:

- Developed a JEDI statement for the club.
- Launched the club from 5 founding members to 25 active members.
- Raised more than \$10,000 in club funds in the first year.

Responsibilities:

- Establishing branding and curriculum for the club's image.
- Envision and pursue the mission of education, practical application, and community collaboration.

Key Accomplishments:

- Completed and closed 3 international projects.
- Followed rigorous guidelines for community engagement and involvement throughout project work.

Responsibilities:

- Maintaining social, financial, and environmental sustainability of all 4 engineering projects.
- Engaging internal and external stakeholders about project health and progress.

Habitat for Humanity Wake County – *Volunteer Consultant* – August 2019 to December 2019 *Key Accomplishments:*

- Completed 3 interactive GIS maps relating property values, public transportation, and Habitat for Humanity housing projects.
- Presented findings and recommendations to Habitat for Humanity Wake County Board of Directors.

Honors and Certifications

North Carolina State University Caldwell Fellow – Class of 2022 Certified NC State Campus Conversations Project Facilitator – 2021 Wilderness First Responder –December 2021